<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><!--
  ~ Petals APP
  ~ Copyright (C) 2021 Leonardo Colman Lopes
  ~
  ~ This program is free software: you can redistribute it and/or modify
  ~ it under the terms of the GNU Affero General Public License as published by
  ~ the Free Software Foundation, either version 3 of the License, or
  ~ (at your option) any later version.
  ~
  ~ This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful,
  ~ but WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of
  ~ MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.  See the
  ~ GNU Affero General Public License for more details.
  ~
  ~ You should have received a copy of the GNU Affero General Public License
  ~ along with this program.  If not, see <https://www.gnu.org/licenses/>.
  -->
<resources>
    <string name="know_the_local_laws_title">Know the local laws</string>
    <string name="know_the_local_laws_content">Understand the legal status of marijuana in your jurisdiction.\nBe aware of the amount you are legally allowed to carry.\nKnow the difference between medical and recreational possession where applicable.</string>

    <string name="carrying_marijuana_title">Carrying marijuana</string>
    <string name="carrying_marijuana_content">Carry it in a closed, non-accessible container when traveling.\nHave your medical marijuana card with you if you are a registered patient.\nBe aware of the areas where possession is illegal (e.g., federal lands, schools, certain public places).</string>

    <string name="use_of_marijuana_title">Use of marijuana</string>
    <string name="use_of_marijuana_content">Do not use marijuana in public places unless explicitly allowed by local law.\nAvoid driving or operating heavy machinery after using marijuana.</string>

    <string name="medical_use_title">Medical use</string>
    <string name="medical_use_content">Always have your documentation ready if you’re a medical user.\nBe familiar with your rights to use, possess, and possibly grow marijuana for medical purposes.</string>

    <string name="interacting_with_police_title">Interacting with the police</string>
    <string name="interacting_with_police_content">If stopped by police, be polite and respectful.\nYou are not required to consent to a search unless the officer has a warrant or probable cause.\nKnow your rights but also understand the potential consequences of asserting those rights (See "Legislation and Rights" below).</string>

    <string name="detained_or_arrested_title">Detained or Arrested</string>
    <string name="detained_or_arrested_content">Stay calm and do not resist.\nYou have the right to remain silent and the right to an attorney.\nDo not provide any details or admit to anything regarding your marijuana use or possession until you have legal representation.</string>
</resources>